A Guide to the Agricultural Development Council records, Record Group 1 FA078
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Research and Training Network, 1953-1977; 3
  - Research and Training Network - Grants, 3.3
    - University of Ceylon - Amerasinghe, Nihal, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Ceylon Association for the Advancement of Science, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Chang, Yen-tien, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Chiengmai University - Disguised Unemployment in a Chiengmai Village, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Chinese Research Institute of Land Economics - Farm Labor Survey, 1956-1959 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Chinju National Agricultural College - Potentials of Hog Supply, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Chonnam National University - Farm Management Survey, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Chonnam National University - Farm Management Survey Supplement, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Chulalongkorn University - Ayutthaya Project, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Chulalongkorn University - Field Training, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Chulalongkorn University - Training Program, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Columbia University - Department of Chinese and Japanese, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Columbia University - Halpern, Joel, 1958-1960, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Columbia University - Koizumi - Travel, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Congres Pour la Liberte de la Culture - East-West Music Encounter, 1956-1961 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Cornell University - Agricultural Economics, 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Cornell University - Agricultural Economics, 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Cornell University - Agricultural Economics - Participants, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Cornell University - Agricultural Economics - Participants, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Cornell University - Beqiraj - Social Change in Albania, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Cornell University - Local Government, 1956-1962 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Cornell University - Sharp - Local Self-Government in Thailand, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Cornell University - Sisler - Travel, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Cornell University - Travel - Cruz, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Council on Social Work Education - Training of Personnel for Overseas Programs, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Council on Social Work Education - Training of Personnel for Overseas Programs, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - University of Dacca - Land Utilization Study, 1955-1960 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Dandekar, V. M., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Delhi School of Economics - Farm Village Economy Survey, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - East Pakistan Geographical Society, 1960-1965 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - English Language Education Council - Japan Society, Inc., 1963-1968 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - English Language Education Council - Japan Society, Inc., 1963-1968 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - English Language Exploratory Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - English Language Exploratory Committee - Individuals, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Estevez, Jose S., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Agricultural Development in Japan, 1961-1967 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Center on Land Problems in Asia and the Far East, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Extension Methods Course - Los Banos, 1957-1961 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Farm Management and Land Use Seminar, 1965-1968 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Farm Management Development Center - Bangkok, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Farm Management Development Centers - Byers, 1955-1957 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Farm Management Development Centers - Financial Data, 1954-1961 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Farm Management Development Centers - Manila, 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Farm Management Development Centers - Manila, 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Farm Management Development Centers - New Delhi, 1955-1957 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Farm Management Development Centers - Pasto, 1956-1959 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Farm Management Development Centers - Saigon, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Farm Management Development Centers - Tokyo, 1955-1957 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Farm Management Workshop - Bangkok - Travel, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Yang - Method of Farm Management Investigations, 1955-1961 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Yang - Method of Farm Management Investigations, 1955-1961 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) - Yang - Method of Farm Management Investigations, Revised, 1961-1969 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Far Eastern Association - Monograph Series, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Gadjan Mada University - Agricultural Economics Workshop, 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Gadjan Mada University - Agricultural Economics Workshop, 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Gadjan Mada University - Bureau of Economic Research, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Gadjan Mada University - Economics Faculty - Travel, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Gadjan Mada University - Post-Graduate Workshop, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Goodfriend, Arthur - Travel, 1954-1956 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Haverford College - Fraser - Barpali Community Development Project, 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - University of Hawaii - Coordinated Studies in Indonesia and Pakistan, 1968-1975 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - University of Hawaii - East-West Philosophers' Conference, 1957-1960 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - University of Hawaii - Travel - Shukla, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Hokkaido University - Agricultural Economics Library and Reading Room, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Hokkaido University - Farm Management Research Training Institute, 1956-1958 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Hokkaido University - Farm Management Research Training Institute, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Hokkaido University - Farm Management Research Training Institute - Visiting Professors, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Hokkaido University - Market Research Training Institute, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Hokkaido University - Rice Production Survey - Takayama, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Hokkaido University - Rice Production Survey - Takayama, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - University of Hue - Price Differentials Survey, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Hutabarat, M. S. - Travel, 1962-1966 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Hutasoit, J. H. - Travel, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Hwang, Eui-gak - Travel, 1970-1972, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Hwang, Ki Hyun - Travel, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - India International Centre, 1961-1966 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Indian Society of Agricultural Economics - Competence of Economists, 1961-1975 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Indian Society of Agricultural Economics - Competence of Economists - Reports, 1961-1975 (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - Indian Society of Agricultural Economics - Cost Study Problem Seminar - Farm Experiment, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Indian Society of Agricultural Economics - Farm Planning Seminar, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - University of Indonesia - Bogor Institute of Agriculture - Bureau of Extension, 1963-1968 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - University of Indonesia - Bogor Institute of Agriculture - Bureau of Extension, 1963-1968 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - University of Indonesia - Bogor Institute of Agriculture - Extension Project - Equipment, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - University of Indonesia - Bogor Institute of Agriculture - First National Conference of Agricultural Economics, 1964-1966 (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - University of Indonesia - Bogor Institute of Agriculture - First National Conference of Agricultural Economics - Supplies, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Capital Formation, Credit, Rice Marketing Studies, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Capital Formation on Rice Producing Farms, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Credit and Indebtedness Study, 1963-1969 (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Credit Structure in Rice Producing Villages, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Karawang Community Development Project, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - "Planning for Agricultural Growth in Sukabumi-district, West Java-province, Indonesia", 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Hadiwidjaja - Travel, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 134)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Post-Graduate Agricultural Social Science Course, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 135)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Post-Graduate Short Course, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 136)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Rice Production and Marketing Study, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 137)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Rural Modernization Symposium, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 138)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Rural Sociology Seminar, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 139)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Soeharjo Capital Formation Study, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 140)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Sudjanadi - Travel, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 141)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Sukabumi Materials, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 142)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Teaching Materials, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 143)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Travel - Clifton R. Wharton Lectures, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 145)
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor - Wilpotan Survey Project, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 146)
    - Institute of International Education - Khanna, 1962-1964 (Box 10, Folder 147)
    - Institute of International Education - Oregon State Summer Workshop - Students, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - International Association of Agricultural Economists, 1962-1972 (Box 10, Folder 149)
    - International Association of Agricultural Economists, 1962-1972 (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - International Association of Agricultural Economists, 1962-1972 (Box 10, Folder 151)
    - International Association of Agricultural Economists - Travel, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 152)
    - International Association for Agricultural Economics in Japan, 1960-1967 (Box 11, Folder 153)
    - International Association for Agricultural Economics in Japan, 1960-1967 (Box 11, Folder 154)
    - International Association for Agricultural Economics in Japan, 1960-1967 (Box 11, Folder 155)
    - International Association of Agricultural Librarians and Documentalists - World Agricultural Economics and Rural Sociology Abstracts (Box 11, Folder 156)
    - International Association of Agricultural Librarians and Documentalists - World Agricultural Economics and Rural Sociology Abstracts (Box 11, Folder 157)
    - International Association of Agricultural Librarians and Documentalists - World Agricultural Economics and Rural Sociology Abstracts, 1959-1964 (Box 11, Folder 158)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 159)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Australia - Asian Grantees, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 160)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Australia - Asian Grantees (B-Y), 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 161)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Australia - U. S. Grantees (A-W), 1967 (Box 12, Folder 162)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Australia - U. S. Grantees (A-W), 1967 (Box 12, Folder 163)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Australia - U. S. Grantees - New York Meeting, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 164)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Australia - U. S. Grantees - Reports, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 165)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Australia - U. S. Grantees - Travel, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 166)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Cuernavaca, 1959-1961 (Box 12, Folder 167)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Cuernavaca - Asian Fellows not Visiting U.S., 1961 (Box 12, Folder 168)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Cuernavaca - Seminar for Asian Fellows, 1958-1961 (Box 12, Folder 169)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Cuernavaca - Seminar for Asian Fellows - By Country, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 170)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Cuernavaca - Visiting Asian Fellows to U.S., 1961 (Box 13, Folder 171)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Cuernavaca - Visiting Asian Fellows to U.S., 1961 (Box 13, Folder 172)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Cuernavaca - Universities, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Fund for, 1965-1968 (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Lyons, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 175)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Mysore, 1955-1959 (Box 13, Folder 176)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Mysore, 1955-1959 (Box 13, Folder 177)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Mysore - Delegates, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 178)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Mysore - Delegates (A-W), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 179)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Mysore - Delegates (A-W), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 180)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Mysore - Hosts, by Country, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 181)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Mysore - Misc. (Box 14, Folder 182)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Mysore - Reports (A-Y), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 183)
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - Mysore - Reports (A-Y), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 184)
    - International Cultural Centre, 1961-1963 (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Iowa State University - Mubyarto - Travel, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Jamil, Mohamed Bin, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 187)
    - Japan Society, Inc. - Exhibit House, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 188)
    - Japan Society, Inc. - Industrial Design Show, 1956-1959 (Box 15, Folder 189)
    - Japan Society, Inc. - Lieberman - Travel, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 190)
    - Japan Society, Inc. - Survey of Language Problems, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 191)
    - Japan Society, Inc. and English Language Exploratory Committee, 1958-1962 (Box 15, Folder 192)
    - Kampto, Utomo - Travel, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 193)
    - Kanungo, Kissen - Travel, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Kasetsart University - Agricultural Economics Department - Assistants, 1958-1965 (Box 15, Folder 195)
    - Kasetsart University - Agricultural Economics Department - Secretaries, 1961-1966 (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Kasetsart University - Economic Analysis Production and Marketing - Corn, 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - Kasetsart University - Farm Management Research Study in Korat, 1958, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Kasetsart University - Labor Use Study, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - Kasetsart University - Land Improvement Societies - Korat, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Kasetsart University - Paddy Marketing Study, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 201)
    - Kasetsart University - Production and Marketing Problems Publication, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 202)
    - Kasetsart University - Regional Specialization and Demand Analysis of Agricultural Products, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 203)
    - Kasetsart University - Thisyamondol, Pantum, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Kasetsart University - Travel - Econometric Workshop, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Keio University - Institute of Management and Labor Studies, 1961-1968 (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - Keio University - Institute of Management and Labor Studies - Reports (A-T) (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Keio University - Institute of Management and Labor Studies - Reports (A-T) (Box 15, Folder 208)
    - Khon Kaen University - Analysis of Peanut Production Using Traditional Practices, 1972-1976 (Box 16, Folder 209)
    - Khon Kaen University - Socio-Economic Survey for Student Training, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 210)
    - Kim, Chung-yup - Travel, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 211)
    - Kim, Dong Hi - Travel, 1967-1968, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 212)
    - Kim, Dong Hi - Travel, 1967-1968, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 213)
    - Kim, Hi Soon - Travel, 1963-1969 (Box 16, Folder 214)
    - Kim, Jeong Bae - Travel, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 215)
    - Koh, Theam Hee - Travel, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 216)
    - Koo, Chun Sur - Travel, 1966-1969 (Box 16, Folder 217)
    - Government of Korea - Ministry of Agriculture and Forestry - Office of Rural Development, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 218)
    - Government of Korea - Travel - Oh and Lee, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 219)
    - Korea Food and Agriculture Organization - National Farm Management Training Center, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 220)
    - Korean Agricultural Economics Association - Conference, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 221)
    - Korean Agricultural Economics Association - Journal of Agricultural Economics, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 222)
    - Korean Agricultural Economics Research Institute - Training Program, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 223)
    - Krishna, Raj - Travel, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 224)
    - Kuo, Leslie T. C., 1954-1958 (Box 16, Folder 225)
    - Kuo, Leslie T. C., 1954-1958 (Box 16, Folder 226)
    - Kuo, Leslie T. C., 1954-1958 (Box 16, Folder 227)
    - Kyoto University - Far East Committee for Correspondence on Methods of Teaching Farm Management, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 228)
    - Kyoto University - Methods of Teaching Farm Management Conference, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 229)
    - Kyoto University - Methods of Teaching Farm Management Conference, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 230)
    - Kyoto University - Methods of Teaching Farm Management Conference, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 231)
    - Kyoto University - Methods of Teaching Farm Management Conference, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 232)
    - Kyoto University - Research and Extension Based on Farm Accounts, 1959-1963 (Box 17, Folder 233)
    - Kyoto University - Utilization of Farm Accounting Records, 1963-1968 (Box 17, Folder 234)
    - Kyushu University - Agricultural Economics Studies, 1958-1961 (Box 17, Folder 235)
    - Kyushu University - Economic Land Classification and Type of Farming, 1964-1966 (Box 17, Folder 236)
    - Lee, Chung Myun - Travel, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 237)
    - Lee, Kyung Won - Travel, 1969-1972 (Box 17, Folder 238)
    - Lee, Kyung Won - Travel, 1969-1972 (Box 17, Folder 239)
    - Libraire Larousse, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 240)
    - Lin, Lok-chien - Cost of Living, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 241)
    - Mahmood, Naseem - Travel, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 242)
    - Federation of Malaysia - Ministry of Agriculture - Travel, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 243)
    - Federation of Malaysia - Ministry of National and Rural Development - Travel, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 244)
    - University of Malaya - Agricultural Communities Studies, 1962-1965 (Box 18, Folder 245)
    - University of Malaya - Economic Geography of Tapioca in Malaysia, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 246)
    - University of Malaya - Readings in Money and Banking, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 247)
    - University of Malaya - Resource - Use Adjustments by Rural Families, 1959-1961 (Box 18, Folder 248)
    - University of Malaya - Rotating Publication Fund, 1964-1969 (Box 18, Folder 249)
    - University of Malaya - Rubber Processing on Large Scale by Smallholder Producers, 1963-1967 (Box 18, Folder 250)
    - University of Malaya - Rubber Production Expansion of Smallholder, 1962-1965 (Box 18, Folder 251)
    - University of Malaya - Rubber Smallholders Research Project, 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 252)
    - University of Malaya - Student Research in Anthropology and Sociology, 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 253)
    - University of Malaya - Tutorships - Tan and Chan, 1962-1965 (Box 18, Folder 254)
    - University of Malaya - Tutorships - Zulkifli, 1961-1965 (Box 18, Folder 255)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Agricultural Productivity Study, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 256)
    - Medina, Jose C. - Travel, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 257)
    - Michigan State University - Ahmed, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 258)
    - University of Minnesota - Agricultural Economics Summer Course, 1959-1961 (Box 18, Folder 259)
    - University of Minnesota - Ong, 1964-1966 (Box 18, Folder 260)
    - Mohrhardt, Foster E., 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 261)
    - Murray, William G., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 262)
    - Nair, Kusum C. - Travel, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 263)
    - Nasoetion, Andi Hakim - Travel, 1967-1969 (Box 19, Folder 264)
    - Nasol, Ramon - Travel, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 265)
    - National Institute of Agricultural Sciences - Farm Management Planning, 1961-1966 (Box 19, Folder 266)
    - National Institute of Agricultural Sciences - IBM Machines, 1959-1966 (Box 19, Folder 267)
    - National Institute of Agricultural Sciences - IBM Machines, 1959-1966 (Box 19, Folder 268)
    - National Institute of Agricultural Sciences - IBM Machines, 1959-1966 (Box 19, Folder 269)
    - National Institute of Agricultural Sciences - IBM Machines, 1959-1966 (Box 19, Folder 270)
    - National Institute of Agricultural Sciences - IBM Machines, 1959-1966 (Box 19, Folder 271)
    - National Institute of Agricultural Sciences - Land Use and Farm Planning, 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 272)
    - National Institute of Agricultural Sciences - IBM Machines (Box 20, Folder 274)
    - National Institute of Agricultural Sciences - Rural Planning Study - Suzaka City, 1962-1966 (Box 19, Folder 273)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly, Inc. - World Assembly of Youth, American Delegation, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 275)
    - National Taiwan University - Agricultural Marketing Workshop, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 276)
    - National Taiwan University - Economic Study of Land Use in Taipei Area, 1961-1965 (Box 20, Folder 277)
    - National Taiwan University - Hsu, Wen-fu, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 278)
    - National Taiwan University - Mao, Y. K. - Land Consolidation Effects, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 279)
    - National Taiwan University - Preparation for Study - Socio-Economic Changes, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 280)
    - National Taiwan University - Research Institute of Rural Socio-Economics, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 281)
    - National Taiwan University - Study Graduates of College of Agriculture, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 282)
    - National Taiwan University - Wu, C. Y. - Marketing Text, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 283)
    - National Taiwan University and Taiwan Provincial Chung Hsing University - Farm and Home Improvement Extension Training Program, 1961-1963 (Box 21, Folder 284)
    - Nommensen University - Agricultural Development Process Study, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 285)
    - Nopporo College of Dairy Agriculture - Wantanabe, 1963-1967 (Box 21, Folder 286)
    - University of North Sumatra - Brastagi Extension Project, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 287)
    - Obihiro Zoothechnical University - Tenma, 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 288)
    - Obihiro Zoothechnical University - Tenma, 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 289)
    - Ohio State University - Agricultural Economics Summer Course, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 290)